kineo.com 2018-08-30

# Disclaimer & Website Policies

Kineo is committed to protecting your privacy. We abide by the Data Protection Acts to protect information about our clients. By using the Kineo website, you consent to the collection and use of information by Kineo, as described below.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of information that is placed on your computer, tablet or phone when you visit certain websites, including this one. These cookies allow us to distinguish you from other users - which makes the site work properly - and to monitor the health of the site. Find out more about cookies on the ICO website.

We use the following types of cookie:

Session cookies - these are deleted when you finish browsing our website  
Persistent cookies - these are stored on your computer after you have finished browsing our website so that we can recall your preferences the next time you visit.  
Cookies used for analytics and performance monitoring are a mixture of session and persistent cookies, but they do not contain any personal information.

If you continue to use our site, we presume that you are happy to receive all its cookies. If not, most browsers allow you to turn off cookies; to do this, check the 'help' menu on your browser, but note that switching off cookies may affect site operation and you may not be able to access some parts of our site.

If you delete cookies relating to this site we will not remember things about you, including your cookie preferences, and you will be treated as a first-time visitor when you come back.

If you have any questions or comments regarding this policy, please email [info@kineo.com](mailto:info@kineo.com)

## Privacy policy

**What information do we collect?**

Kineo Limited (we or our or us) will be the ‘controller’ of the personal data you provide to us. We only collect basic personal data about you and this does not include any special types of information, nor specific location - except for your postal address, if you provide it.

The information we collect about you through this site is limited to that entered on any form. This may include your name, place of work, building address, email address, telephone number and other contact details.

**Why we need this information**

We need to know your basic personal data to provide the services or information requested - this may be about our products, for upcoming events, on product and service updates or changes, or to provide a response to specific questions asked.

We may also use anonymous aggregate information, cookie data and statistics to help monitor site performance and usage, to make the site operate correctly and to help plan improvements. Some of this anonymous information may be passed to the third parties who work with us to maintain the site.

**Processing your data**

All the personal data we process is handled by our staff in the UK and is located on servers in the UK. No third parties have access to your personal data unless the law allows them to do so. Kineo processes your data within the framework of our Electronic Information Security Policy and General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) compliance documents – copies of which can be downloaded from this site.

**Keeping your data**

We keep your personal data for marketing and other purposes related to the reason for your initial contact, until you notify us that you no longer wish to receive these communications. You may unsubscribe at any time by contacting us at info@kineo.com or by using the ‘unsubscribe’ link at the foot of any marketing email we send. You can also unsubscribe by contacting the main Kineo office by phone or letter. Contact us for details.

**Your further rights**

Regarding the information we process on you – if you believe the information is incorrect and want it amended, wish to receive a copy, want to have it deleted, or wish to make a complaint on how we have handled it, you can contact our Operations Director who will investigate the matter. Email info@kineo.com.

If you are not satisfied with our response, or believe our processing of your personal data is not in compliance with the law, you can complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO).

**Changes to our privacy policy**

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email.

**Links from this site**

Our site may contain links to the websites of our partners, affiliates, or other third party organisations. If you follow a link to a third party website, we recommend that you review its privacy policy before submitting any personal information there.

**Contact us**

Please email info@kineo.com if you have any questions regarding this privacy policy.

Our site may contain links to the websites of our partners, affiliates, or other third party organisations. If you follow a link to a third party website, we recommend that you review its privacy policy before submitting any personal information there.
